<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>CocoaPods Blog</title>
		<description>Updates for the fascinating developments happening in the CocoaPods world.</description>
		<link>http://blog.cocoapods.org</link>
		<atom:link href="http://blog.cocoapods.org/feed.articles.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			
				<title>Cocoa Kucha - 20 Nov 2013</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;CocoaPods is more than just a tool, CocoaPods is a community of over a thousand &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/CocoaPods/Specs/graphs/contributors&quot;&gt;commiters&lt;/a&gt;, six thousand Podspecs and hundreds of thousands of &lt;a href=&quot;http://rubygems.org/gems/cocoapods&quot;&gt;users&lt;/a&gt;. To say the community is growing is a mild &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/CocoaPods/Specs/graphs/code-frequency&quot;&gt;understatement&lt;/a&gt;. One of the cool things about a big community is that there&amp;#39;s the chance that people will get clumped enough together to make meeting up and sharing ideas a possible. I&amp;#39;d like to announce our first attempt at trying to bring people together, starting in New York City this November.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>  
        
        
				<pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
				<link>http://blog.cocoapods.org/Cocoa-Kucha</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.cocoapods.org/Cocoa-Kucha</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
				<title>CocoaPods 0.26</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we are releasing CocoaPods 0.26.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most visible change is that CocoaPods now hides the schemes of the Pod
targets. If this doesn&amp;#39;t ring a bell the following image should.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog_img/CocoaPods-0.26/schemes-comparison.png&quot; style=&quot;display:block;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>  
        
        
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
				<link>http://blog.cocoapods.org/CocoaPods-0.26</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.cocoapods.org/CocoaPods-0.26</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
				<title>On Design</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;CocoaPods is arguably one of the most important open source project in the Objective-C community. It&amp;#39;s used in thousands of applications and has hundreds of thousands of downloads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Building the tool, the community and the ecosystem around the project has happened organically with a mix of people coming and helping out to get us to a position where CocoaPods is essential to any project. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting from May 2013, I&amp;#39;ve been working with &lt;a href=&quot;http://andy-myers.co.uk&quot;&gt;Andy Myers&lt;/a&gt; to try and re-think the systems around CocoaPods, ranging from how we do documentation to the branding. This blog post is to open up our process a bit and to explain how we came to some of these ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>  
        
        
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 02:20:16 +0100</pubDate>
				<link>http://blog.cocoapods.org/redesign</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.cocoapods.org/redesign</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
				<title>Why we don't accept donations</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: While we very much appreciate the sentiment, the project (as an entity) does not accept financial donations. &lt;/p&gt;

</description>  
        
        
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2013 02:20:16 +0100</pubDate>
				<link>http://blog.cocoapods.org/Why-we-dont-accept-donations</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.cocoapods.org/Why-we-dont-accept-donations</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
				<title>Using Acknowledgements</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;CocoaPods will generate two &amp;#39;Acknowledgements&amp;#39; files for each target specified in your Podfile. If the pods are coming from the master repo, then they must include one. Private pods don&amp;#39;t require one. These contain the License details for each Pod and for most of the part having them in your acknowledgements will be enough to conform to the license.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CocoaPods generates a markdown file for general consumption, as well as a property list file that can be added to a settings bundle for an iOS application. You don&amp;#39;t need to do anything for this to happen, it will just work. If you&amp;#39;d like to know more about extra things you can do with this, read on.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>  
        
        
				<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
				<link>http://blog.cocoapods.org/Acknowledgements</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.cocoapods.org/Acknowledgements</guid>
			</item>
			
		
	</channel>
</rss>
